A Guide to the Lester M. Salamon Papers FA1868
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Related Projects, 1967-2021; 8; 25.25 Cubic Feet (67 containers)
  - Agenda Setting in Putin's Russia, Salamon and Benevolenski, 2011-2018 (Box 79, Folder 810)
  - United Nations Handbook Implementation - Luxembourg/Spain, 2019-2021 (Box 79, Folder 811)
  - RD3 Poor - Correlation/Regression, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 814)
  - RD3 - Advocacy Correlation/Regression, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 815)
  - Panel Change of Revenue by Source, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 816)
  - Panel Change in Expenditures, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 817)
  - RD1-RD3 Change in Expenditure, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 818)
  - Panel Change in Expenditure - Real Percentage Change, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 819)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - Overview, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 820)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - Phase 1 Theory Paper, 1995-1996 (Box 80, Folder 821-822)
  - Comparative Book - Social Origins of Civil Society, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 823-824)
  - Leverage for Good - Proofed, undated (Box 81, Folder 825)
  - PRI Institute, Baltimore, Maryland, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 828)
  - Johns Hopkins Comparative Nonprofit Sector Project - Phase II and IIB Project Guidance Manual, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 829-830)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Drafts, 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 831-836)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy Book: Cross-Cutting Issues, 2010-2011 (Box 83, Folder 841-842)
  - Poverty Amidst Plenty: The Two Faces of Anne Arundel County, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 843)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy: New Tools, 2010-2011 (Box 84, Folder 844-845)
  - Mississippi, undated (Box 84, Folder 846-847)
  - Russia Higher School of Economics - Civil Society Research Lab, 2014-2016 (Box 85, Folder 848-849)
  - Protest and Revolution in the Rural South: Black Organizational Development, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 850-851)
  - Mississippi Draft, undated (Box 85, Folder 852-853)
  - General CCSS, 2003-2009 (Box 86, Folder 854-855)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - New Actors, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 856-858)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - New Actors, 2009-2010 (Box 87, Folder 859-861)
  - NVSQ Symposium Articles, NRU Higher School of Economics, 2019 (Box 87, Folder 864)
  - Outsourcing Social Services to CSOs: Lessons from Abroad, 2009 (Box 87, Folder 865)
  - FP 7/Third Sector Impact Project - WP2: Conceptualizing the Third Sector in Europe, 2014 (Box 89, Folder 874)
  - FP 7/Third Sector Impact Project - WP3: Measuring the Third Sector in Europe, 2014-2015 (Box 89, Folder 875)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy I - New Players, 2008-2009 (Box 89, Folder 876-877)
  - Russia Higher School of Economics - Year 3 Papers and Special Edition, 2016 (Box 90, Folder 881)
  - Size Sector Analysis, Chapter 2, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 882)
  - Quality 2000: Government and Business Roles Task Force Meeting #1, 1993 August 3 (Box 91, Folder 885-887)
  - NAPA Privatization Paper Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 91, Folder 888)
  - Johns Hopkins Comparative Nonprofit Project - Overview Report, undated (Box 92, Folder 889-890)
  - Child Care Readings, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 891-892)
  - National Nonprofit Book - Chapter 5: Advocacy, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 893-894)
  - National Nonprofit Book - Chapter 6: Poor, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 895)
  - National Nonprofit Survey Methodology (RDS I, II, III), 1990-1993 (Box 93, Folder 896)
  - Nonprofit Sector Binder, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 897-898)
    Contains sections on private giving, higher education, arts and culture, advocacy, and foreign aid.
  - Primer 1992 Version (Box 93, Folder 899-900)
  - Field Guide Summaries, 2014 (Box 95, Folder 906)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Readings, 2012 (Box 95, Folder 907-910)
  - The New Alliance for Progress: Corporate Social Engagement in Latin America - Prinzhorn Case Reports, 2007 (Box 97, Folder 919-920)
  - Political Risk Rating and FDI Workshop, 2017-2019 (Box 97, Folder 921)
  - Rotary Volunteer Measurement Project, 2018-2019 (Box 97, Folder 922)
  - Nonprofit Development in Hong Kong: The Case of the Statist-Corporatist Regime, undated (Box 97, Folder 923)
  - Global Civil Society, Volume III, 2008 (Box 98, Folder 924)
  - Country Chapters: Advanced Market Economics, 2001-2004 (Box 98, Folder 925-927)
  - The Resilient Sector: The State of Nonprofit America - A Summary, undated (Box 99, Folder 930)
  - The Resilient Sector: The State of Nonprofit America - Chapter 1 Comments, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 931-932)
  - The Resilient Sector: The State of Nonprofit America - Introduction, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 933-934)
  - The Resilient Sector: The State of Nonprofit America - Introduction Kelafur Edits, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 935)
  - The Resilient Sector: The State of Nonprofit America - Copyedited Version, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 936)
  - Education and Training, Donald M. Stewart, 2001-2002 (Box 99, Folder 937)
  - Donald M. Stewart, 2011-2002 (Box 100, Folder 938-939)
  - Housing and Community Development - Avis Vidal (Nonprofit America), 2000-2002 (Box 100, Folder 940)
  - Margaret Wyszomirski (Nonprofit America), 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 941-942)
  - Dennis R. Young, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 943-944)
  - Lipman-Hearne - State of Nonprofit Sector, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 945)
  - Primer of Nonprofit Sector - U.S. Social Services Spending, 1950-1985, undated (Box 101, Folder 946)
  - FY 1988 Budget, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 947)
  - What Corporate Welfare Costs - Donald L. Barlett, TIME, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 948)
  - New Governance and Tools in China, Chinese Public Administration, 2009 (Box 101, Folder 949)
  - Johns Hopkins International Fellows in Philanthropy Program, Fellows Journal, 2003 Spring (Box 101, Folder 955)
  - Grants-in-Aid Briefing Book, CDBG, NIDCD and New Start Grants, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 956)
  - Frontiers of Philanthropy - Draft, undated (Box 101, Folder 958)
  - The Investment Policies of Foundations, Ralph L. Nelson, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 959)
  - The Preparedness Challenge in Human Assistance, A Report to the Center on International Cooperation, New York University, 1998-1999 (Box 102, Folder 960)
  - Global Humanitarian Emergencies: Trends and Projections, 1999-2000 (Box 102, Folder 961)
  - UNBH and New Frontiers of Philanthropy, China, 2019 (Box 102, Folder 962)
  - Gingrich - 1994/1995 Congress Elections (Box 102, Folder 963)
  - Holiday Letter, Johns Hopkins University, 1999-2015 (Box 102, Folder 964)
  - Project Planning Book, 1989-1990 (Box 102, Folder 965)
  - Policy Tools and Government Performance Conference Report, Washington, D.C., 2002 (Box 102, Folder 966)
  - Community Foundations, 2002-2003 (Box 102, Folder 969)
  - Criminal Justice Administration as Rubik's Cube: Managing the Multi-Sector Delivery of Criminal Justice Services, Richard Culp, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 970)
  - American Review of Public Administration SAGE Publications, Volume 33, Number 2, 2003 (Box 102, Folder 971)
  - The New Governance, Public Administration Review (PAR) Article - Comments, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 972)
  - Point Form Outline for VSI Impact Evaluation Report, Caroline DeWitt, 2006 (Box 103, Folder 973)
  - UN TSE Sector Handbook Flyers, undated (Box 104, Folder 998)
  - The Resilient Sector Revisited Flyers, undated (Box 104, Folder 999)
  - Explaining Civil Society Development: a social Origins Approach Flyers, 2018 (Box 104, Folder 1000)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy Flyers, 2018 (Box 104, Folder 1001)
  - Nonprofit Works Flyers, undated (Box 104, Folder 1004)
  - Johns Hopkins Center for Civil Society Studies Nonprofit Employment Report, 2020 (Box 104, Folder 1005)
  - Ford Foundation Proposals, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 1006)
  - Listening Post Project - Council on Foundation Meeting Fact Sheet, 2002 (Box 104, Folder 1007)
  - Listening Post Project - Expansion, 2011 (Box 104, Folder 1008)
  - Listening Post Project - Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 1009)
  - Listening Post Project - General, undated (Box 104, Folder 1010)
  - Health Benefits Communique, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 1011)
  - CIVINET - Handbook of Nonprofit Institutions Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 1012)
  - CIVINET - Philanthropy Fellow Fact Sheet, 2002-2003 (Box 104, Folder 1013)
  - CIVINET - University Commitment Letters, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 1014)
  - CIVINET - Fact Sheet, undated (Box 105, Folder 1015)
  - CIVINET - Briefing Ford/Skoll Foundation Meeting, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 1016)
  - Civil Society Future - State of the Nonprofit Sector Project, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 1017)
  - Civil Society Future - State of Sector Advisory Group, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 1018)
  - Civil Society Future - Civil Society Renewal Project, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 1019)
  - Civil Society Future - Five Year Program Plan, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 1020)
  - Civil Society Future - Civil Society Center Plan, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 1021)
  - Civil Society Future - Data Network, 1998-1999 (Box 105, Folder 1022)
  - Civil Society Future - Monitoring the Health of the Nonprofit Sector: Towards a New Data System, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 1023)
  - Ford Foundation Reserve Fund Request, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 1024)
  - Center for Civil Society Studies (CCSS) Program Plan, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 1025)
  - Civil Society and the Solution of Public Problems: A Four Country Assessment, Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 1026)
  - Center for Civil Society Holiday Letter, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 1027)
  - Ford CNP Phase III Request, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 1028)
  - The Third Sector in Latin American: An Emerging Force, undated (Box 105, Folder 1029)
  - Oxford Global Civil Society Book, 2002 (Box 105, Folder 1030)
  - Oxford University Marketing Questionnaire, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 1031)
  - UN and Phase III Projects, 2002 (Box 105, Folder 1032)
  - Spouses of Heads of State and Government Conference, Mexico, 2002 (Box 105, Folder 1033)
  - CIVINET (Civil Society Information Network), 2001-2002 (Box 105, Folder 1034)
  - CIVINET - Proposal, 2002 (Box 105, Folder 1035)
  - CIVINET - Budgets, 2001-2005 (Box 105, Folder 1036)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data (NED) Project - Fact Sheet, undated (Box 106, Folder 1037)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB) Consultant Agreement, 1979-1980 (Box 106, Folder 1038)
  - Nonprofit Capital Op-Ed, 2002-2003 (Box 106, Folder 1039)
  - Urban Institute, Nonprofit Governance Report, 2004-2006 (Box 106, Folder 1040)
  - Capital Needs Op-Ed, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 1041)
  - Listening Post Project - Nonprofit Investment Capital Needs, undated (Box 106, Folder 1042)
  - Conference on Policy Tools and Government Performance, Washington, D.C., 2002 April 11-12 (Box 106, Folder 1043)
  - Nonprofit Governance, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 1044)
  - Listening Post Project - Powerpoint Summary, undated (Box 106, Folder 1045)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 1: Taking the Pulse of the Nonprofit Sector, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 1046)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 2: Stressed But Coping: Nonprofit Organizations and the Current Fiscal Crisis, undated (Box 106, Folder 1047)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 3: The Health Benefits Squeeze: Implications for Nonprofit Organizations and Those They Serve, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 1048)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 4: Nonprofit Governance and Accountability, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 1049)
  - Nonprofit America: An Overview, Congressional Briefing/ASPEN, 2006 March (Box 106, Folder 1050)
  - Alliance for Nonprofit Healthcare, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 1051)
  - Nonprofit Capital Arnova Slides, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 1052)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 5: Investment Capital: The New Challenge for American Nonprofits, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 1053)
  - Listening Post Project - Workforce Communique Presentation, 2008 (Box 106, Folder 1054)
  - Tradeable Tax Credits for Job Creation, 2010 (Box 107, Folder 1055)
  - Getting Beyond the Nonprofit Blues, Abramson and Salamon, undated (Box 107, Folder 1056)
  - Nonprofit Workforce, SSIR Draft, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1057)
  - Listening Post Project - Advocacy Presentation, 2008 July (Box 107, Folder 1058)
  - Health and Pension Benefits Results, 2009 (Box 107, Folder 1059)
  - Workforce Roundtable Release, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1060)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 9: Nonprofit America: A Force for Democracy, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1061)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 10: A Nonprofit Workforce Action Agenda, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1062)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 11: Nonprofit Policy Priorities for the New Administration, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1063)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 12: "Shovel-Ready" But Stalled: Nonprofit Infrastructure Projects Ready for Economic Recovery Support, 2009 (Box 107, Folder 1064)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 13: Listening Post Project Roundtable on Nonprofit Advocacy and Lobbying, 2009 (Box 107, Folder 1065)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 14: Impact of the 2007-09 Economic Recession on Nonprofit Organizations, 2009 (Box 107, Folder 1066)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 15: Health Care and Nonprofits: The Hidden Dimension of American's Health Care Crisis, 2009 (Box 107, Folder 1067)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 16: Escalating Pension Benefit Costs - Another Threat to Nonprofit Survival?, 2009 (Box 107, Folder 1068)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 17: Nonprofits, Innovation, and Performance Measurement: Separating Fact from Fiction, 2009-2010 (Box 107, Folder 1069)
  - Listening Post Project - Communique 20: The Nonprofit Technology Gap - Myth or Reality?, 2008-2010 (Box 107, Folder 1070)
  - Forward Together: Empowering America's Citizen Sector for the Change We Need, undated (Box 107, Folder 1071)
  - Listening Post Project - Pilot Communique, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 1072)
  - Taxes and Charity, 2012 (Box 107, Folder 1073)
  - Nonprofit Values Flyers, 2013 (Box 107, Folder 1074)
  - Susan Dreyfuss, 2014-2015 (Box 108, Folder 1076)
  - TechSoup Profile, 2012-2013 (Box 108, Folder 1077)
  - TechSoup Work, 2010-2013 (Box 108, Folder 1078)
  - Nonprofits and UN Sustainability, 2014-2015 (Box 108, Folder 1079)
  - Toward A Global Civil Society Information System - Mott Foundation Proposal, 2015 (Box 108, Folder 1080)
  - U.S. Nonprofits - Kresge Foundation Proposal, 2015 (Box 108, Folder 1081)
  - Toward A Global Civil Society - TechSoup Global, Johns Hopkins University Center for Civil Society Studies Final Agreement, 2015 (Box 108, Folder 1082)
  - TechSoup Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 108, Folder 1083)
  - FP 7 Nonprofit Global Impact Project, 2013 (Box 108, Folder 1084)
  - FP 7 Nonprofit Global Impact Project - Budget, 2014 (Box 108, Folder 1085)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - Data Availability, 2014 (Box 108, Folder 1086)
  - Measuring Social Consequences of Non-Profit Institution Activities, Sokolowski, 2013 (Box 108, Folder 1087)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - To-Do, 2014 (Box 108, Folder 1088)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - Reporting, 2014 (Box 108, Folder 1089)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - Policy Briefing, 2015 (Box 108, Folder 1090)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - WP3 Third Sector Impact (TSI) Data Available Report, 2015 (Box 109, Folder 1091)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - Meeting Dubrovnik, 2015 May (Box 109, Folder 1092)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - EU Intern, 2016 (Box 109, Folder 1093)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - Brussels Meeting, 2015 (Box 109, Folder 1094)
  - Conceptualizing Panel, ISTR, 2016 (Box 109, Folder 1095)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - Reporting Period 2, 2017 (Box 109, Folder 1096)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - Travel, 2014-2016 (Box 109, Folder 1097)
  - FP 7 Third Sector Impact Project - WP3 Size of Sector, 2015-2016 (Box 109, Folder 1098)
  - Global Civil Society III, 2012 (Box 109, Folder 1099)
  - Global Civil Society - Chapter 1: Introduction, 2014-2015 (Box 109, Folder 1100)
  - Global Civil Society - Social Origins Revision, 2010-2015 (Box 109, Folder 1101)
  - Global Civil Society III - Chapter 3, 2015 (Box 109, Folder 1102)
  - Global Civil Society III - Chapter 3 Revisions, 2008-2009 (Box 109, Folder 1103)
  - Social Origins of Civil Society Update, undated (Box 109, Folder 1104)
  - Global Civil Society III - Chapter 2 Revisions, 2015 (Box 109, Folder 1105)
  - Civil Society and Volunteers: The Foot Soldiers for the SDGs, 2016 (Box 109, Folder 1106)
  - Global Civil Society III - Editor Comments, undated (Box 110, Folder 1107)
  - Social Origins Articles, 2009 (Box 110, Folder 1108)
  - European Volunteer Measurement Project, 2011 (Box 110, Folder 1109)
  - UN Handbook - Revisions, 2009-2015 (Box 110, Folder 1110-1111)
  - UN Handbook - Nonprofit Institutions Chapter, 2008 (Box 110, Folder 1112)
  - UN Handbook - Revisions - impact Chapter, 2016 (Box 110, Folder 1113)
  - UN Handbook - Revisions - Flyers, undated (Box 110, Folder 1114)
  - UN Handbook - Warsaw Conference, 2016 October (Box 110, Folder 1115)
  - Canada - I-Lab HSE Nonprofit Sustainable Conference, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 1116)
  - Russia Regional Project, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 1117)
  - Panama - Tools and Nonprofit Institution Handbook, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 1118)
  - Russia - Political/Economy Articles, 2016 (Box 110, Folder 1119)
  - Serve America Act, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 1139)
  - White House Nonprofit Working Group, 2013 (Box 112, Folder 114)
  - Resilient Sector II - Data, 2015 (Box 112, Folder 1147)
  - Value of Nonprofits Communique, 2012 (Box 112, Folder 1148)
  - Nonprofits and Federal Budget - FY 2006, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 1149)
  - Nonprofits and Government - Budget Chapter, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 1150)
  - Social Responsibility Credit Exchange, 2009-2010 (Box 112, Folder 1151)
  - Recommendations to IRS - 990 Form and Aspen Data Group, 2016 (Box 112, Folder 1152)
  - The 2019 Nonprofit Employment Report (Box 112, Folder 1156)
  - Nonprofit Workforce Labor Day Release, 2019 (Box 112, Folder 1157)
  - Nonprofit Works, 2016 (Box 112, Folder 1158)
  - Maryland Nonprofit Employment Reports, 2001-2004 (Box 112, Folder 1159)
  - Nonprofit Works: An Interactive Database on the Nonprofit Economy, Mott Foundation, 2017 (Box 113, Folder 1160)
  - Nonprofit Employment Project, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 1161)
  - Nonprofit Employment: What Do We Know? What Do We Need to Know?, undated (Box 113, Folder 1162)
  - Nonprofit Employment - South Carolina Report, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 1163)
  - Nonprofit Employment - Washington Report, 2004-2005 (Box 113, Folder 1164)
  - Nonprofit Employment - What Nonprofit Wage Defecit?, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 1165)
  - Nonprofit Wage Comparison, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 1166)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - In Search of the Nonprofit Sector: Improving the State of the Art, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 1167)
  - Nonprofit Employment - Minnesota Report, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 1168)
  - Nonprofit Employment - Virginia, 2008 (Box 113, Folder 1169)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Fact Sheets, undated (Box 113, Folder 1170)
  - Nonprofit Employment - Colorado Report, 2008 (Box 113, Folder 1171)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Monthly Labor Article, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 1172)
  - Charitable Giving among Wealthy, 2009 (Box 113, Folder 1173)
  - Nonprofit Employment in Recessions, undated (Box 113, Folder 1174)
  - National Nonprofit Employment, 2004-2006 (Box 113, Folder 1175)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Michigan, 2009 (Box 113, Folder 1176)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - State Reports, 2001-2008 (Box 114, Folder 1177-1178)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Florida Report, 2007-2008 (Box 114, Folder 1179)
  - Nonprofit Employment - Maryland Recession, 2001-2008 (Box 114, Folder 1180)
  - National Nonprofit Report - Employment in America's Charities, 2004-2006 (Box 114, Folder 1181)
  - Nonprofits and Recessions, 21 States, 2001-2010 (Box 114, Folder 1182)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - 2010 Report, 2010-2011 (Box 114, Folder 1183)
  - Budget Realities, 2011-2012 (Box 114, Folder 1184)
  - Nonprofit Employment - Interactive Data, 2013 (Box 114, Folder 1185)
  - Westchester Nonprofit Project, 2013-2014 (Box 115, Folder 1186)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Virginia Conference, 2012 (Box 115, Folder 1187)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Holding the Fort: Nonprofit Employment during a Decade of Turmoil, 2012 (Box 115, Folder 1188)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Washington, D.C. Conference, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 1189)
  - Nonprofit Employment - Maryland, 2011-2014 (Box 115, Folder 1190)
  - Nonprofit Works - Phase 2, Ancilla Partners, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 1191)
  - New York City Nonprofit Study, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 1192)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics Meeting, 2015 June (Box 115, Folder 1193)
  - Casey Foundation, 2013-2015 (Box 115, Folder 1194)
  - Nonprofit Works Business Model, Ancilla Partners, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 1195)
  - Maryland and Anne Arundel County Nonprofits, 2012-2016 (Box 115, Folder 1196)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 1197)
  - Nonprofit Employment Data Project (NED) - Budget Supplement, 2015-2016 (Box 115, Folder 1198)
  - Nonprofit Works Materials, 2010 (Box 115, Folder 1199)
  - Civil Society Index Paper - Studying Civil Society, Heinrich, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 1200)
  - Civil Society Index Paper, 2003-2004 (Box 115, Folder 1201-1202)
  - Civil Society Index Paper - CIVICUS Index, 1999-2001 (Box 115, Folder 1203)
  - USAID Civil Society Index, 2010 (Box 116, Folder 1204)
  - USAID NGO Sustainability Index, Sub-Sahara Africa, 2010 (Box 116, Folder 1205)
  - NGO Sustainability Index, Central and Eastern Europe and the New Independent States, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 1206)
  - Carnegie Report, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 1207)
  - The Resilient Sector - Press Release, undated (Box 116, Folder 1208)
  - The Resilient Sector - Op-Ed, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1209)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Peggy Outon, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1210)
  - Nonprofit Futures: Alliance for Children and Families, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 1211)
  - The Resilient Sector - Harvard Business Review, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1212)
  - The Resilient Sector - Flyers, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1213)
  - The Resilient Sector - The State of Nonprofit America - Preliminary Draft, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 1214)
  - The Resilient Sector - Level the Financial Playing Field for Nonprofits, undated (Box 116, Folder 1215)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Reviews, 2003-2004 (Box 116, Folder 1216)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Overview Chapter, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1217)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Postcards, undated (Box 116, Folder 1218)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Surdna Foundation, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1219)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Progress Report, Mott Foundation, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1220)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Congressional Briefing, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1221)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Outreach Activity Update Report, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 1222)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Dissemination, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 1223)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Book Cover Sample, undated (Box 116, Folder 1224)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Nonprofit Quarterly, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 1225)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Intro Chapter, LMS Edits, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 1226)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Chapter Summaries, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 1227)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Progress Report, Packard Foundation, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 1228)
  - The Resilient Sector - Press Release, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 1229)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Chapter 3, Education and Training, undated (Box 117, Folder 1230)
  - The Resilient Sector - Manuscript Edits, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 1231)